This is so cool!
right yes that's right also team McGraw is in it which he is a very famous
country singer he's married to Faith Hill and Kathy Bates which is great great
actress and it's a really good movie it's a make you feel good movie make you
feel good inspiring movie exactly okay so basically the movie is set in a city
where you know people with money live and there's a school that decides to
open up a program that allows underprivileged people to or children to
join or to come to that school and study and that's where this boy comes in he's
an african-american boy comes to study at that school and it turns out that he's a
great football player yeah well the thing what I like about the movie is like it
start out with this kid just going there and actually he's going to the school and
the school is all white people you know it's like it's very rich school because
it's private is Christian it has a lot of money right so then he comes there and
you can see that he has no money nobody takes care of him he has his family it's
well they don't don't care for him you know so then he starts hanging out with
this little kid waist younger and at some point the mother of this kid which
is played by Sandra Bullock looks at him and he's like who is this guy right and
just like that helps him and after I don't know where yeah that's what I like
about the movie it's it's great to see that there's really good hearted people
that do things because out of love pure simple love alright so Sandra Bullock
starts to help out this kid and well we're not gonna spoil the end of the
movie and actually this movie is in theaters now so it's a very new movie but
it's very well received I think it's been nominated for Golden Globes Sandra Bullock
actually won the Golden Globe for best best lead female leading role and she
also won an award for the Actors Guild yeah sag and now she's nominated for an
Oscar and the movie too and the movie too yeah that movie it's it's nominated
as best movie best picture yeah wow so it's the fight now is the blindside
avatar which other movies nominated blindside avatar hurt locker hurt locker
okay and what's the other one I think a single man I don't I don't remember oh
really okay so but do you think which movie do you think will take the Oscar
for best picture avatar avatar I'm pretty sure you don't you didn't really like
avatar I loved it I really don't think it's worthy of winning an Oscar no
because I think Oscar should be about you know the movie if it moves people you
know if it's uh if it has a message to his I don't know it should be more
serious not like oh yeah it's about blue people in a world and that's it you know
mm-hmm I just think it has so last year slumdog millionaire was the one that won
best picture exactly that makes sense that makes sense you like that one yeah
because it shows you like the real India you know and it makes everything it makes
love it makes all this mafia under that exploit venture adventure music
photography everything yeah you know avatar it has that but it's still there
should be like maybe a place for it where it's like a best action movie or
something like that then okay but how can I don't know well I guess it's hard
because I think it's hard for an action movie to to win best picture so because
obviously if you think about it most times the Oscars go to drama films
they're always dramas but that's exactly my point because they're trying that's
that's why I think it should be because they're always trying to perceive reality
and show it in a way of entertainment you know not as drama not as like the
news that you watch it and you want to cry okay but this the blindside is also
a drama it is a drama but it's a it's about you know the American dream
basically what the movie is is giving someone a hand you know helping someone
and then by themselves they can do wonders so it teaches you that how if
you help people then they just need a little push right sometimes and then
they will do it on their own so that's what I liked about so it has a good
message right it helped people and you know to not be selfish I mean if you
have if you have enough then maybe you can share with others and it's a true
story and after the movie ends you see pictures of the real family the real
events and it's it's based in in real events and also they didn't just do
that they didn't just help him now they have a foundation and that's what
they're doing and it's great you know because these people they're like
millionaires if they didn't want to do anything they would just like spend all
their money and that's it right right so it's I think it's great okay very good
so it's a new movie as I said it's out in theaters probably you would have to go
to the movies and see it if you want to catch it but it's definitely a film
that's worth watching right that's definitely a movie that's worth paying a
ticket to go to the movies okay so we recommend this film we go out and see
it and if you have any other questions or you want to recommend a movie that you
would like for us to talk about then come to our website englishpod.com or drop us
an email and we'll see everyone next time